[♪ epic theme music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[birdsong]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Tully's been here.
We found one of their camps
just ahead.
But something...
strange has happened there.
[insects buzzing]
They're all Rivermen.
Who killed them?
We found no sign of their foe.
They did not fall here.
[shouting]
On your guard!
It's a trap!
[all shouting. grunting]
-[choking]
-To me!
[shouting]
Aaah!
[grunts]
Ah!
[shouting]
[swords clanging]
Yah!
[groaning]
[panting]
We light the way!
[all shouting]
[banging]
[slow. repetitive banging
continues]
This was not the battle.
[slow. repetitive banging
continues]
Who are they?
-Our death.
-[banging continues]
[Oscar Tully]
Criston Cole!
Traitor. usurper.
and defiler of justice.
Come forth to hear your fate.
If I strike my banners.
will you spare my men their lives?
-[chuckles]
-I made a promise to the dead. Cole.
I told them I'd build a sept
out of traitors' bones.
I don't have
near enough bones yet.
Hm.
If there is to be battle here.
many of you will die as well.
That's why we've come.
What better way to die
than blade in hand?
As you will it.
[♪ somber music playing]
Let us begin here then.
One of me
against the two of you.
[groaning softly]
Will that be enough
to make a fight of it?
[arrow thwacking]
♪♪
[soldiers shouting]
[♪ somber music
continues playing]
♪♪
[guard]
They're here.
[sighs]
I mourn my friend Ser Luthor.
and some four and 10
of his best men.
A total count of five and 20
of the City Watch
now slain in the name
of "King Daeron."
Lord Ormund mocks us
in our own city.
He means to show the realm
that I cannot govern
even my own seat.
The great houses watch
while he humiliates me.
Where is my army?
Ser Criston has hindered them.
The vanguard is still
a fortnight's march from Tumbleton.
The insult must be answered now.
We must do what we
should have done in the first.
Burn the villains out.
Then Ormund gets what he wants.
A queen who murders
loyal subjects cannot be trusted.
We know where the traitor
has entrenched himself.
If I fly directly
to the Footly stronghold...
[Lady Sabitha]
On a dragon. I presume.
A beast well known
for its delicacy
and precision in battle.
Ah. yes. what a marvel.
The flame it spews forth
can discern with pure magic
who is blameless
and who is deserving...
[metal clanging]
I'll hear no more from those
whose greatest battle
has been
with their own indigestion.
[Alyn]
I am of the same mind as the lord
and ladies. Your Grace.
Your army marches ever nearer.
You will answer
this outrage with force
but discriminately...
-if we wait but a while longer.
-[Daemon] At what cost?
Remember the prophecy.
your sacred calling.
Whatever you do in its service
is justified.
Aegon the Conqueror
burned thousands
on the Field of Fire. thousands.
and settled the realm
for generations...
The Conqueror
burned enemy soldiers.
not subjects who bent the knee.
Their lord bent the knee to you!
The people would just
as happily follow a mule
-if that same...
-My father would abhor it.
Ah. and there we have it.
But...
my patience has its bounds.
-I will send knives.
-[Daemon] So be it.
At least I will get to meet
the fiend face-to-face before he dies.
Oh. no. not you.
I will have my satisfaction.
Yes.
But the most effective assassin
has a plain face.
Fanatics still prowl the streets
outside our castle gates
at Lord Ormund's bidding.
That is your charge.
Your Grace. there is
a detachment left here
of Velaryon men. soldiers.
ready to aid
Prince Daemon in his...
I think not.
How many Velaryon men
remain in King's Landing?
Some threescore. Your Grace.
Petition your father for more.
They may be needed
to secure the city.
Who then will you send
to Tumbleton?
It is a dangerous errand.
and one that will require force.
[Ser Lyonel] My queen. the delegation
from House Baratheon has arrived.
Your Grace. I am sent
to represent House Baratheon
in response to your summons.
Where is Lord Borros?
Lord Borros begs patience.
my queen.
He has taken his army
to the Red Mountains
to fight the Vulture King.
who has been raiding
the Stormlands these many moons.
His queen summons him north.
and all of a sudden it occurs
to him that he must ride south.
It is my lord's duty
to guard the realm
against the Dornish threat.
As it was his duty
to guard my son
when he came to treat
with him beneath his roof?
Once the Vulture King
has been subdued...
Your lord makes the mistake
of considering a common bandit
a greater threat
to his interests than I am.
I could brand him a traitor
and hang you in his stead.
No disrespect was intended.
Your Grace.
to you or your endeavors.
It is but... but a matter
of time.
Time?
If there were aught else
I could offer you at this moment.
I would lay it before you
most willingly.
Give me your belt.
[Vermithor bellowing]
[people chattering]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[chittering]
[dragons chittering]
Anything to report?
[chuckles softly]
Market day tomorrow.
Do you remember Market Day
in King's Landing?
Before all of this?
[dragons continue chittering]
Fruit stalls.
Geese honking.
Traders shouting.
[sighs] Hot pies.
Took it all for granted.
didn't we?
It will soon be
the same again. I imagine.
But we're not the same. are we?
We weren't in service back then.
At the beck and call
of the queen
sleeping on a hill... alone.
She stopped me
going to the tavern. Hugh.
Not one ale with the lads.
What's the point
in having a dragon
if no one's around to see it?
Well. would you go back
to where you were?
Scrabbling around in the dust?
-No.
-Mm.
Though I can't say my life
has been improved.
Can you?
[scoffs lightly]
Right. then. [grunting]
[sighs] See you in two days.
Ser Hugh.
[whistling] Come on. girl.
[door opens]
Leave us.
You would have done the same.
Have I not shown you mercy
even before those who named
my kindness to you a weakness?
Are you so ungrateful
-that you insist upon...
-Helaena is with child.
So. you flee.
To preserve the babe's life.
and Helaena's with it.
[scoffs] Still you insist
on misjudging me.
If the child is male.
would you not in the end
find it necessary?
To hold him hostage.
at the least?
To draw out Aemond or...
or Ormund in his pride?
Or simply to secure
your own reign from endless challenges.
You were discovered by guards.
I cannot let this go unanswered.
Helaena did
as I persuaded her to do.
If you must be cruel.
let it be me who suffers.
Only spare her.
You must both now
be more strictly confined.
Your guard is doubled.
There'll be no more walks
in the Godswood.
-I accept this judgment for myself...
-My judgment
does not require
your acceptance.
Rhaenyra. you know what she is.
She is fragile.
you... you cannot confine her.
I didn't!
And now. I must!
She cannot be seen.
If she is known
to carry Aegon's heir.
I will be forced to do
what you fear.
Well. so. so. so send us
away then to some remote...
Away? Now?
Your son is still at liberty.
Your cousin wreaks chaos
within my city walls.
Even today. I must answer
another of his murderous treasons.
You are a Hightower.
To my court. you are the enemy.
And to you?
Do not try me.
-[sighs]
-[door opens]
What did she tell you?
Helaena is with child.
Are there others who know?
I believe not.
You yourself had no suspicion?
No.
♪♪
That one.
A thief and a liar.
Let me know when it's done.
We will be avenged.
If it takes a hundred years.
What's this?
Forgive me. my prince.
This is how you answer?
With desertion?
The queen asked for loyalty.
and I was willing enough
to wait.
But my children
are now penniless.
I will not leave them
fatherless as well.
Small wonder Hightower vermin
swarm our streets
when they smell
your craven stink.
My first duty
must be to my family.
I-I will earn our coin
another way.
And when cutthroats
and scoundrels swarm your house.
rip the bread
from your children's mouths.
and take their pleasure
with your wife.
All of you.
You forget what this city was!
Before I turned this rabble
into an army.
before I led you
out of your squalor
and formed you into men!
[whispering] Shame.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[people chattering]
Word in the city is that
you've done valiant work.
The Triarchy raids
have dwindled.
There's more to do.
As ever will be the case.
State your purpose. Alyn.
Ormund Hightower strikes
insidiously at King's Landing.
seeking to throw it into chaos.
The City Watch is buckling.
I would send to Driftmark
to shore up their number
with good Velaryon men.
So. she asks more of me.
It is I who ask.
Do as you have said.
Her needs are endless.
Have you not exhausted
your anger yet?
You take her side...
when she yet refuses
to grant you legitimacy.
And how many years did it
take you to do the same?
I have heard things...
in questioning these pirates.
Tell her Tyland Lannister
survived the Gullet...
and is making for Rook's Rest.
[shovel digging]
[grunting]
-That's enough.
-The dogs will find him.
They're welcome to him.
By the time they come.
we'll be gone.
But not far.
And if the others realize...
If you wish to dig deeper.
Lord Larys.
the shovel is free.
I have found passage to Braavos
on a merchant cog
out of Maidenpool.
We must draw as little notice
as we can for a few days
as we provision ourselves.
but...
I believe we can sail
before the full moon.
I must interject. my king.
I still feel
it would be an error
for you to leave Westeros.
You would be best served
at Casterly Rock.
where we can establish a court
and enjoin those
still loyal to you.
Do you think
I'm a terrible man. Ser Tyland?
I would never say...
That is...
while I may not have always
agreed with every course of...
Um. well...
[Tyland stammering]
There is...
in any one of us. I venture...
much to admire
and much to be deplored.
[clicking tongue. sighs]
Mm.
We sail for Essos. then.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[wind whistling]
[Sheepstealer calls]
[dragon shrieks]
[dragon chirping]
For your face.
It's been long since anyone
sought to defend me.
I am in your debt.
As I am apparently in yours.
But I'm glad I can leave here
now with that score settled.
Where do you think to go?
I need to find my dragon.
She would not have
left me willingly.
and I'll not be without her.
A frog in winter
sleeps under the ice.
Still and silent.
Mend your wounds.
Gather your strength.
Let the world think you dead
until the spring thaw.
I need to find a horse.
To ride where?
Over the numberless leagues
of the Seven Kingdoms?
Vhagar will come to me.
It is perhaps this forsaken
castle she shuns.
Or if not.
I'll go to King's Landing.
It's said she haunted
the hills outside the city
in the years before I was born.
There is a bounty on your life.
Every sellsword
is combing the woods
hoping to slit your throat
in the night.
Oh. and half
the commonfolk. too.
Even you must sleep.
There's no place for you
to rest your head.
And nor am I safe here then.
Or you. for harboring me.
Is it possible that Vhagar
flew away
as a way of protecting you?
Without her. you're hidden.
The queen assumes that
where your dragon is...
there you will be. too.
She is no queen.
And when you find your mount.
will you fly to your death?
Rhaenyra has six dragons
to your one.
You'll fall alone.
And to what end?
[person screaming]
Never ceases to be fascinating.
[door opens]
As you ordered. my lady.
What did I say.
when last we met?
I saw Moondancer...
my sister's dragon.
flying towards Iron Oaks.
And what does that
to do with you?
She's my sister. I...
I thought if I could
just see her face.
So you leave your hiding place.
in violation of our agreement.
and you fly toward a town equipped
with several thousand pairs of eyes.
all watching and wondering
what your appearance portends.
I didn't even see her.
She was already gone.
And what do you think
would have happened if she hadn't?
The queen thinks
Sheepstealer's rider is dead.
It has been your only reprieve.
If word reaches her...
Have you forgotten already
the doom that hangs over you?
And over me.
For harboring you.
For allowing myself
to be swayed.
-I'm sorry.
-Mm.
All my life.
I have yearned after a dragon.
And now I have one.
but I have lost everything else.
That was your choice.
They are dead to you now.
But you got
what you wanted. Go.
And the next time
you try me will be the last.
[dragon screeching. bellowing]
A bed would be more comfortable.
My lady.
I'm going.
I just needed
a little more time.
I know what it is
to be so weary.
[clearing throat]
I. uh... saw my father today.
I was wondering
if you would speak to him.
There is a distance there.
as if he's removed
himself entirely.
I just thought...
maybe now he might. um...
see me.
I thought the same
with my father.
They cannot face their ghosts.
so they seek to outstrip them.
Even if they leave us behind.
They roam. they punish.
they fight. they do.
[sighs]
I cannot help him. Alyn.
I have my own burdens to bear.
I. uh... [clearing throat]
You should go to bed.
You're very dutiful.
I am the eldest.
It must get wearisome...
attending to everyone else
all the time.
Maybe a little.
Don't you ever want
to forget it all?
Do what you want?
[♪ gentle music playing]
And so. Ser Criston fights on.
and yet you have returned.
Because...
Because fighting on is madness.
Do you think me mad. Your Grace?
No. sire.
Hm.
[Gwayne]
You mean to fight on?
With what?
There's a dragon
sitting on the hill above us.
and five more
not 30 leagues away.
Rhaenyra will not burn
her own subjects.
She is a woman.
Squeamish.
If your host
leaves these walls. it burns.
Aemond has fled
and Rhaenyra holds my sister hostage.
The River army
draws closer by the day.
[knocking on table]
What possible course is there?
Your uncle lacks imagination
as well as courage.
I would take one Hightower sword
over three of Tully's mudmen.
When the usurper's host
comes here.
we will fight on our terms.
on our ground.
We have the clear advantage.
Meanwhile. we are turning
King's Landing
against that overweening cunt.
little by little. bite by bite.
Exposing her as weak
and unsuited to rule.
The great houses cannot
but come to our side.
Have any yet come?
The patient hunter
gets the kill.
Something the craven among us
would do well to learn.
I have marched a long road.
fought and killed.
and suffered my comrades
to be killed about me.
Yes. you have endured much.
I'm sure you found solace with
some of your brothers in arms.
I am fatigued.
It's been weeks
since I've seen a feather bed.
By your leave.
You might see Ser Gwayne
to his quarters. Your Grace.
Make sure he bathes.
Oh. and. uh...
[whispering]
Mind yourself.
Backs against the wall.
-"Your Grace"?
-I'm sorry. I had to get through it.
And this is your way?
Fawning?
Daeron.
He's styled you the bloody king.
You left me alone with him.
You know what he is.
I do what I can
to keep him from...
you know.
I had no choice.
No.
But neither did it grieve you
to ride away.
I hate what I am
when I'm with him.
A puppet. a fool. a child.
And yet he means
to put you on the throne. apparently.
Only as he cannot
sit on it himself.
No. he would thrust me forward
and devour me from within
until there's nothing left.
So tell him you won't do it.
Then who will protect me then?
Will you raise an army
against his savages?
If you were king.
you could cast him down.
I will never be king. uncle.
we both know it.
[sighs] I need to lie down.
-You'll stay. won't you?
-And do what?
Bear witness whilst Ormund
marches our house to its doom?
I'm second in line.
I shall return to Oldtown
and prepare to pick up
the pieces.
Don't leave me again.
Please.
You're his little treasure now.
You'll be fine.
When you were in
King's Landing...
Did you see my mother?
[Alicent] Will you not eat?
You have taken nothing
since yesterday
and said little more.
[softly] Helaena.
Mysaria knew of our plan.
but she said nothing
of Jaehaera.
Was she truly stolen away
to meet us
at some secret place up ahead?
I see.
Forgive me. Helaena.
The... the road ahead
was fraught with peril.
-To bring a small child...
-You lied.
I wished only to save you
from this place.
Me?
Or yourself?
What difference does it make?
I have come too far.
I have sacrificed too much.
If I cannot at long last
salvage my daughter...
Helaena. please.
Please. you must eat.
[♪ somber music playing]
[horse neighing]
[softly] One-Eye.
-[blade stabbing]
-[gasps]
I have kept your secret.
I will keep it still.
You could have killed me. too.
And claimed Rhaenyra's bounty.
There are many things
I could have done to you.
Then what is this game you play?
It's yours to learn.
If your spirit is willing.
[chest dragging]
Have you forgotten your history?
Dreamfyre.
Your ancestor
Rhaena Targaryen
came to Harrenhal
after the death of her daughter.
And she grieved
and grew old here.
Her dragon laid a clutch of eggs
before Rhaena herself died.
and they have sat here.
cold and abandoned
these hundred years.
I do not know
the ways of dragons.
but I have long envisaged
the return of the Targaryens
to this ancient seat.
[rain falling]
I have been cursed for my sins.
Alys.
All I put my hand to
withers beneath its touch.
Do you imagine that you alone
know what it is to be cursed?
I'm tired of this
desolate existence.
And so. I think. are you.
[thunder rumbling]
You've been alone
your whole life. Aemond.
Can you not imagine...
what it would be...
to have it otherwise?
[Aemond] It's warm.
There's an ancient
strength here.
Let the gods turn
their backs on us.
We will make our own fortune.
I will be the Lady of the Water.
[sighs]
And you...
the dragonlord by my side.
But in the meantime.
you're a Targaryen prince.
And your sons
will be Targaryen princes
in their turn.
♪♪
[baby crying]
Tallow is scarce
and cost thrice what it did.
We cannot light our sconces.
You know my response.
Ser Torrhen Manderly
is Master of Coin.
It is his task now to distribute
what resources we have.
I suggest you address
Ser Torrhen himself.
Bring the next.
Your Grace.
The motherhouse
lately enjoyed the protection
of the City Watch.
Now. we are in peril.
One of our girls
only last night was taken.
You have my condolences.
I shall...
light a candle for her
when next I attend the sept.
[crowd murmuring]
Godric. Your Grace.
A mason.
We have watched in fear
as we found gold cloaks
murdered among us.
and I have heard
a great number of 'em
have resigned their posts.
leaving the streets undefended.
Yes. these are Hightower crimes.
The craven Ormund strikes at me
from Tumbleton.
where he has concealed himself
among innocents.
[Godric] This we know.
But how will we now
be protected?
If the City Watch fails.
then who will preserve order among us?
I have sent for Velaryon men
-to root out the enemy within our walls.
-[crowd clamoring]
Once they arrive.
the city shall be returned...
[townsperson]
How will they be protected?
-[clamoring continues]
-[septa] She was but six and 10!
[Godric]
Your Grace. we are afraid.
And wherever the fault lies.
we have none
to look to now but you.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[crowd continues clamoring]
[clamoring continues]
[people chattering]
[chattering continues]
Daemon Targaryen.
How many?
How many of you are there?
-How many?!
-We have no number.
We are everywhere.
What did Ormund Hightower
promise you. gold?
Huh?
A place at his table
when he takes the throne?
There is a king waiting
just outside these walls.
And until Daeron the Daring
takes his rightful place.
we will not rest.
Then your kind
will die in dragonfire.
or trampled down by my army.
Will she lay waste
to her own city?
Will she set upon her own people
with swords?
You'll never find us.
We're the people
of the Seven Kingdoms.
We have no sign or sigil.
And when you strike us.
you only drive more
to our cause.
You rebel against one
who has neither wished
nor done you harm.
You can burn us.
You can kill us.
You will never make us
embrace her.
[groans]
Watch where you're fucking...
Your prince.
Uh. Your Grace.
What is your errand here?
I... I was... I thought...
I... I was just...
I'm taking the air.
Are you not commanded to stay
in the Keep under guard?
Well. yes.
In a manner of speaking.
Insolent maggot.
I'm up that bloody hill
for days at a time.
Men deserve
their simple pleasures.
Keep us going.
You yourself should understand...
-[grunting]
-[crowd gasps]
-[groaning]
-Set foot in the city again.
and I'll put out your eyes.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[chatter resumes]
[hoofbeats approaching]
[horse neighing]
Ho. there.
Ho. Friend.
[soldier] Come on!
Put your backs into it!
[indistinct shouting]
Come on!
[soldiers chattering]
All clear!
Here.
[Ormund]
The common man is. as a rule.
of no interest or concern.
But you must never trust one
who's clawed his way to power.
His ambition is oft fueled
by some lack.
Some shame. or lust. or rage.
Mm.
You should think on it
when you choose your Hand.
Rhaenyra made a rare good choice
with Corlys Velaryon.
There is a soundness
to his breeding.
Not the sordid appetite
of the striver.
What of my grandsire?
Otto? [chuckles]
Where do I begin?
My lord. House Baratheon
sends an envoy
to treat with the new king.
Let the Stormlands lead the way.
Highgarden will have no choice
but to follow.
[sighs] Stand up.
Stand up. both of you!
Lord Ormund Hightower.
Beacon of the South.
Defender of the Citadel.
and Voice of Oldtown.
Well met. Ser Ormund.
I come as an envoy
of Lord Borros Baratheon.
Lord Paramount
of the Stormlands.
Mm.
[clearing throat]
-You are quite welcome. Ser...
-Ser Arrion Baratheon.
Cousin to Lord Borros.
I most regret presenting
ourselves to you in this state.
The road was long and filthy.
but I thought it best
to speak to you immediately.
We are honored to receive you.
And what word from Lord Borros?
Well. House Baratheon
bends the knee to His Grace.
King Daeron Targaryen.
and offers its many banners
in alliance
with House Hightower.
I have been ordered
to swear fealty
to the new king
on behalf of Lord Borros.
Your lord has made
a wise choice.
If we might see
the king in person.
that we may bend the knee
before him.
His Grace. Daeron Targaryen.
The First of his Name.
King of the Andals.
the Rhoynar and the...
-[blade slashing]
-No! Stop him!
-[men shouting]
-Stop him!
-No!
These are assassins.
sent for Daeron and you.
-[flesh squelching]
-[grunting]
[splatting]
-[swords clanging]
-[men shouting]
[grunting]
Ser Arrion Baratheon
has hair of light chestnut.
He's about a foot taller.
and as it happens...
-[blood streaming]
-far more comely.
[thud]
I will cleave the bitch
from crown to cunt.
She will die
wishing she never dared...
Dared...
[retching]
Kat.
[sighs]
I thought you were d-dead.
[Kat whimpering]
[sobbing]
I looked for you.
I went home. but you'd gone.
What choice did I have?
I was alone.
I escaped in the chaos.
I came here to my brother.
And now. he's dead. too.
But Kat. I've done it.
I claimed a dragon.
Vermithor. the Bronze Fury.
I've been made a knight.
And the queen has promised...
Is that what this is?
Dragon?
-You smell different.
-We'll have coin now.
A fine house. anything you wish.
I can take you
out of this to safety.
Do you not see?
Your husband is a dragonrider.
Do you know
how many days it takes...
to walk the road here
from King's Landing?
Do you know what may befall
a woman alone on that road?
Did something happen?
Many things happened.
While you were on Dragonstone...
-seeking out your own glory.
-I did it for you.
I didn't want it!
I needed you here.
On the ground.
[whispering] I'm sorry. I am.
But I... I can stay no longer.
If I am discovered here...
Just come with me.
I won't forsake my family.
There is no time.
Come. we're going.
-No!
-I will not leave you in peril.
-What are you doing?
-[shushing]
[muffled shouting]
Who are you?!
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
-[people shouting]
-[swords clanging]
[Ormund] You did well.
I treated you harshly.
and for that. I'm sorry.
The strains of the campaign.
You may return to Oldtown
if you wish.
A small band of men
won't attract the attention of the dragons.
-I'll not stop you.
-[Daeron] There are three of you.
Should be easy.
Again.
[shouting. clanging resumes]
[Gwayne]
He'd make a good king.
Not that that matters to you.
You think me so callous.
I think you'd sacrifice lives
to feed your own pride.
But I know you'd never
sacrifice your own.
So. tell me.
What is your plan here?
Speak your purpose.
Helaena.
She cannot stay confined.
Her state of mind is precarious.
her condition being what it is.
Do you have something useful
for me. or have I been misled?
I know where Aemond is.
-All this time?
-O-Only... only lately.
I would need a guarantee
that we'd go free.
Both of us.
as originally agreed.
You're in no place to demand
guarantees of anything.
When Aemond is gone.
your reign is assured.
Ormund will surrender or die.
Helaena and I
are no threat to you.
We will disappear.
You will not hear of us again.
Where is he?
Harrenhal.
My riders have searched
for Vhagar there
-half a dozen times.
-I did not say I know where Vhagar is.
How did you come by this?
There are times when Helaena...
when Helaena sees things.
It will sound mad.
They are nightmares
or... or puzzles.
But the things she does see
now and then. they come to pass.
She dreams.
She's a dreamer.
Like Daenys
who foresaw the Doom.
If what you say is true.
if Aemond has separated
somehow from his dragon...
then...
he is one man on foot...
and being hunted.
He will have hidden himself
so he cannot be found.
I have told you all that I know.
His capture must now
fall to you and your council.
No.
If I send swords...
he will flee again.
go to ground.
and be lost. but...
If I send just one sword...
with someone he trusts...
No. I will...
I will be no part of this.
-No. please. Rhaenyra.
-Unhand her Grace.
I...
I... I cannot leave Helaena.
I will keep watch over her.
Until you return.
Did I not warn you...
that you would come to this?
I don't want to be alone.
[sighs] Nor do I.
I have no choice.
Here.
You could refuse.
And Aemond would
still be like to die.
Do you not wish to be free?
Why am I here?
Was there no other lord
that offered for my hand?
Or was it your own desire
to marry me to my brother?
It was my father's wish.
But I did not begrudge it.
Better here with me. I thought.
than a man you did not know
in a place far away.
Please. Please.
We still have some
small chance at freedom. Helaena.
But I cannot go unless I know
you are sustained.
[sighs]
Please.
[softly] There.
I will return to you
as soon as I am able.
I give you my word.
I will come back
and collect you. and we will...
we will walk out in the sun.
[♪ soft. dramatic music playing]
[Orwyle]
Forgive the hour. Your Grace.
There has been a rider
from Tumbleton.
"Kick this dog...
and it will bite your hand."
[soldiers singing indistinctly]
[Corlys]
You have fought like sharks.
Swift and relentless.
We have cut through our enemy
-and routed them!
-[soldiers cheering]
But now. your blades
are needed in the city.
And I...
I have been too long away.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Who are you?
What's your errand?
[Corlys grunting]
[soldiers shouting]
[shouting continues]
[♪ dramatic music intensifying]
♪♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-